With the 98th pick in the 2026 NFL
Draft, the Minnesota Vikings select
Jacoby Thomas, defensive back, Miami.
Yeah, Jacoby [music] Thomas, he's got a
lot of production. You see the five
picks there. He's a real smooth, fluid
mover.
He's got good size, [music] 211 lb, and
you'll see him He's got the ability to
see the future a little bit from the
middle of the field to drive and make
plays. Here he shows you some of the pop
he has as a hitter. And then, here's
those ball skills. Did not catch the
ball well at [music] the combine, CD,
which shocked us because you see all
these ball skills when you're watching
him on tape, but he does play He plays
aggressive, he plays fast. You see it as
a blitzer as he just dump trucks the
running [music] back on the way to the
quarterback. But, a lot of energy and a
lot of ball production.